Welcome to my YouTube channel Guys Hrithik
Technical Support.  In this video we will
tell you how you can make an insurance claim in Bajaj Finance.
Ok.  So first of all
guys,
if you
create your account using the link of Bajaj Finance that we have given you in the description,
then you will get a referral reward of up to ₹5,000.
Ok?  We have opened the Simple app.
Then it will show you this type of
interface.  After coming to the home page,
you can see here that you
get the category of insurance, you have to
click on the insurance one.  Then you
get the last option here to manage your
insurance.  Ok?  You have to
click on the option Manage Your Insurance.
Now after coming here, you have to
click on the sign in option.  You have to sign in here again and again.  Well,
you do
n't have to do it right now.  Now whatever
insurance you have will be shown to you here
and if you want to make a claim then you will
also get the option to make a claim here.
Ok?  Or if you do
not want to claim from here, you will
not get the option to claim.  If your date has not come yet, then
after that you
can simply talk to customer care.  You can simply
take a screenshot of this number.  And if
we have to claim health insurance or any other
insurance, then simply
contact this customer care number.
Share your thoughts with them.  Then
your claim will be made from your insurance.
Ok?  So this is how
you will make insurance claim on Bajaj
Finance.  So, see you in the next video.